<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>study on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/study/</link>
    <description>Recent content in study on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Read the Bible: Repetition</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000066_repetition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000066_repetition/</guid>
      <description>When we read the Bible, a great tool for understanding is watching out for repetition.
Let&#39;s look at just a few examples of how biblical authors can use repetition to cause us to further examine the Scriptures.
Repetition of Words and phrases In the creation narrative found in the first chapter of Genesis, we see God call His creations good a seven times.
This repetition establishes God as the decider of what is good—and by extension what is not good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Bible Translation is Best</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000062_whichbibletranslationisbest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 19:04:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000062_whichbibletranslationisbest/</guid>
      <description>Short answer: There isn&#39;t one. You should read as many translations as you can! But how do you pick one to read right now?
Each translation is trying to strike a balance between being easy to read and understand, and being true to the original language. Some translations are going for a word-for-word representation while others may be going for a thought-for-thought translation. And others are more like a paraphrasing of the original text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The S.P.A.C.E. P.E.T.S. Method for Bible Study</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000050_thespacepetsmethod/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:29:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000050_thespacepetsmethod/</guid>
      <description>What is S.P.A.C.E. P.E.T.S.? Earlier this week, we talked about the S.O.A.P. Method for Bible study. Today, we&#39;ll talk about a method that can go hand-in-hand with it to help us with the &#34;Application&#34; part of the S.O.A.P. Method: S.P.A.C.E. P.E.T.S.
With space pets, you ask yourself if you can find any of these in the text:
  S: Sin to confess  P: Promise to claim  A: Attitude to change  C: Command to obey  E: Example to follow  P: Prayer to pray  E: Error to avoid  T: Truth to believe  S: Something to praise God for  When we try to apply the Bible to our lives, it can seem hard because the Bible is an ancient library of books written by and to an ancient people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The S.O.A.P. Method for Bible Study</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000049_thesoapmethod/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 17:45:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000049_thesoapmethod/</guid>
      <description>When we read the Bible, sometimes we just read the words on the page and move on. But what about when we want to get a little more understanding from the text? Is there a systematic way of breaking down scripture so that we get to its deeper meanings? There are actually many methods for this, but we&#39;ll focus on one today: The S.O.A.P. Method.
What Does SOAP Stand For?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bible Study Tools: Concordance</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000048_concordances/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 09:26:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000048_concordances/</guid>
      <description>What is a Bible concordance? A Bible concordance is an index of words used in the Bible and a reference for where each word occurs within the Bible.
There are many free online concordances, and you can also buy them in print.
 Why would I use a concordance? Concordances are useful for finding passages. Only remember one word from a passage you want to find? Looking for passages that refer to the same topics and concepts as the one you&#39;re reading?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
