<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>In the Storm on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/series/in-the-storm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in In the Storm on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 11:57:39 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/series/in-the-storm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Your Prayer in the Storm</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000040_yourprayerinthestorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 11:57:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000040_yourprayerinthestorm/</guid>
      <description>When we are in crisis circumstance can make us want to rush into action. We run forward to solve problems, forgetting that our first step should be prayer.
Here are a few short prayers that speak God&#39;s Word over our lives. Let&#39;s say what God says in this season.
Overcoming Worry Lord, I thank You for Your logic-defying peace as I come to Your throne.a Because I trust You, I know that You keep me in perfect peace and keep my mind whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Focus in the Storm</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000039_yourfocusinthestorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 11:57:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000039_yourfocusinthestorm/</guid>
      <description>When we are in crisis it can be hard to keep our focus in a healthy place. If we let our thoughts run wild, our fear can overwhelm us. But the Bible lets us know where our focus should lie.
Focus on Jesus We look away from the natural realm and we fasten our gaze onto Jesus who birthed faith within us and who leads us forward into faith’s perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Speech in the Storm</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000038_yourspeechinthestorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 11:56:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000038_yourspeechinthestorm/</guid>
      <description>When we are in crisis, our emotions can come to overtake us, and we speak rashly. But even as you walk through chaos, it&#39;s important to T.H.I.N.K. before you speak.
T: Is it True? Instead, speaking the truth in love, we will grow to become in every respect the mature body of him who is the head, that is, Christ. Ephesians 4:15 NIV
 H: Is it Helpful? Don’t use foul or abusive language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
