<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scripture roundup on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/scripture-roundup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scripture roundup on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/scripture-roundup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Be Humble</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000064_behumble/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000064_behumble/</guid>
      <description>I our fast paced, appearance driven society it can be tempting to seek status above everything else. But what does the Bible say about humility? He leads the humble in justice, And He teaches the humble His way. Psalm 25:9 NASB
 Lift yourself up with pride and you will soon be brought low, but a meek and humble spirit will add to your honor. Proverbs 29:23 TPT
 Humble yourselves before the Lord, and he will lift you up in honor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving is the Key to Receiving</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000061_givingisthekeytoreceiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 12:46:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000061_givingisthekeytoreceiving/</guid>
      <description>Oh, the joys of those who are kind to the poor! The Lord rescues them when they are in trouble. The Lord protects them and keeps them alive. He gives them prosperity in the land and rescues them from their enemies. Psalm 41:1-2 NLT
 Whoever gives to the poor will lack nothing, but those who close their eyes to poverty will be cursed. Proverbs 28:27 NLT
 And whoever gives a cup of cold water to one of my humble disciples, I promise you, he will not go unrewarded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible Promises for Stability in a Shaky World</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000059_stabilityinashakyworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 12:46:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000059_stabilityinashakyworld/</guid>
      <description>I know the Lord is always with me. I will not be shaken, for he is right beside me. Psalm 16:8 NLT
 Stop imitating the ideals and opinions of the culture around you, but be inwardly transformed by the Holy Spirit through a total reformation of how you think. This will empower you to discern God’s will as you live a beautiful life, satisfying and perfect in his eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fruit-Full Life</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000058_thefruitfulllife/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 05:49:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000058_thefruitfulllife/</guid>
      <description>You didn’t choose me, but I’ve chosen and commissioned you to go into the world to bear fruit. And your fruit will last, because whatever you ask of my Father, for my sake, he will give it to you! John 15:16 TPT
 May you always be filled with the fruit of your salvation—the righteous character produced in your life by Jesus Christ—for this will bring much glory and praise to God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Don&#39;t Rush </title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000055_dontrush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 08:07:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000055_dontrush/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s so easy to rush through life, eager to turn the next corner. Or to look back and wonder why it took so long to know what you know now. But the Bible tells us that God is strategic and purposeful about time. Let&#39;s see what wisdom the Bible has for us concerning timing.
There is an appointed time for everything. And there is a time for every event under heaven— Ecclesiastes 3:1 NASB</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What About Your Friends?</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000054_whataboutyourfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 13:32:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000054_whataboutyourfriends/</guid>
      <description>Friendship is so vital to our lives. Let&#39;s look at what the Bible has to say about friends.
Friends Weather the Storm Together  A friend is always loyal, and a brother is born to help in time of need. Proverbs 17:17 NLT
 So never give up on a friend or abandon a friend of your father—for in the day of your brokenness you won’t have to run to a relative for help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bible Wisdom For Patience in Anger </title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000053_promisesforpatienceinanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 12:02:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000053_promisesforpatienceinanger/</guid>
      <description>But don’t let the passion of your emotions lead you to sin! Don’t let anger control you or be fuel for revenge, not for even a day. Don’t give the slanderous accuser, the Devil, an opportunity to manipulate you! Ephesians 4:26-27 TPT  Do you want to be a mighty warrior? It’s better to be known as one who is patient and slow to anger. Do you want to conquer a city?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promises For Comfort in Loneliness</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000052_promisesforloneliness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 12:02:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000052_promisesforloneliness/</guid>
      <description>The Lord is close to all whose hearts are crushed by pain, and he is always ready to restore the repentant one. Psalm 34:18 TPT
 For the Lord your God is living among you. He is a mighty savior. He will take delight in you with gladness.With his love, he will calm all your fears. He will rejoice over you with joyful songs.” Zephaniah 3:17 NLT
 And never forget that I am with you every day, even to the completion of this age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running a Godly Business</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000044_runningagodlybusiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 11:58:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000044_runningagodlybusiness/</guid>
      <description>Running a business can be very stressful, but glory to God for taking the weight. He has given us wisdom for navigating deals and dilemnas! Let&#39;s look at some of the advice the Bible gives us about business.
Remember That it is Really God&#39;s Business It can be easy to think that the businesses we run are ours alone. But the truth is that we are stewarding all that we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution: The Biblical Way</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000043_conflictresoltion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:58:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000043_conflictresoltion/</guid>
      <description>Conflict is just a part of life. We will all at one point or another need tools to resolve it. Let&#39;s have a look at some Godly principles for handling times when we don&#39;t see eye to eye.
Avoid Strife and Argument Whenever Possible  The Bible tells us that we should try to avoid having the argument in the first place. This is not the same as &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Forget to Mind Your Business!</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000028_mindthineown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000028_mindthineown/</guid>
      <description>The Bible is full of practical advice for life. Let’s look at what it says about meddling in other people’s affairs.
It’s better to grab a mad dog by its ears than to meddle and interfere in a quarrel that’s none of your business. Proverbs 26:17 TPT
 Aspire to lead a calm and peaceful life as you mind your own business and earn your living, just as we’ve taught you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
