<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>practical advice on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/practical-advice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in practical advice on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/practical-advice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Subdue the Earth?</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000069_subduetheearth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000069_subduetheearth/</guid>
      <description>Dominion Given In the book of Genesis, we see God give humanity dominion over all of creation. He instruct humans to subdue the earth.a Does this mean we can do whatever we want? After all, we&#39;ve got dominion!b. We are to subdue creation!c
Let&#39;s look in the second chapter for some insight:
And the LORD God took the man, and put him into the garden of Eden to dressd it and to keepe it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catch All the Little Foxes</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000068_catchthefoxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000068_catchthefoxes/</guid>
      <description>Catch all the foxes, those little foxes, before they ruin the vineyard of love, for the grapevines are blossoming! Song of Solomon 2:15 NLT
 Here, the vineyard is the budding relationship between the couple in the poem. The foxes represent issues that tear relationships apart. What lesson can we glean from fox behavior so that me way protect our relationships?
Possessiveness Foxes mark their territory with unpleasant scents and droppings so that other animals know they own the place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Read the Bible: Repetition</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000066_repetition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 19:04:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000066_repetition/</guid>
      <description>When we read the Bible, a great tool for understanding is watching out for repetition.
Let&#39;s look at just a few examples of how biblical authors can use repetition to cause us to further examine the Scriptures.
Repetition of Words and phrases In the creation narrative found in the first chapter of Genesis, we see God call His creations good a seven times.
This repetition establishes God as the decider of what is good—and by extension what is not good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
