<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>practical on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/practical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in practical on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 19:04:11 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/tags/practical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Which Bible Translation is Best</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000062_whichbibletranslationisbest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 19:04:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000062_whichbibletranslationisbest/</guid>
      <description>Short answer: There isn&#39;t one. You should read as many translations as you can! But how do you pick one to read right now?
Each translation is trying to strike a balance between being easy to read and understand, and being true to the original language. Some translations are going for a word-for-word representation while others may be going for a thought-for-thought translation. And others are more like a paraphrasing of the original text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fruit-Full Life</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000058_thefruitfulllife/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 05:49:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000058_thefruitfulllife/</guid>
      <description>You didn’t choose me, but I’ve chosen and commissioned you to go into the world to bear fruit. And your fruit will last, because whatever you ask of my Father, for my sake, he will give it to you! John 15:16 TPT
 May you always be filled with the fruit of your salvation—the righteous character produced in your life by Jesus Christ—for this will bring much glory and praise to God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Don&#39;t Rush </title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000055_dontrush/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 08:07:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000055_dontrush/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s so easy to rush through life, eager to turn the next corner. Or to look back and wonder why it took so long to know what you know now. But the Bible tells us that God is strategic and purposeful about time. Let&#39;s see what wisdom the Bible has for us concerning timing.
There is an appointed time for everything. And there is a time for every event under heaven— Ecclesiastes 3:1 NASB</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What About Your Friends?</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000054_whataboutyourfriends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 13:32:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000054_whataboutyourfriends/</guid>
      <description>Friendship is so vital to our lives. Let&#39;s look at what the Bible has to say about friends.
Friends Weather the Storm Together  A friend is always loyal, and a brother is born to help in time of need. Proverbs 17:17 NLT
 So never give up on a friend or abandon a friend of your father—for in the day of your brokenness you won’t have to run to a relative for help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bible Wisdom For Patience in Anger </title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000053_promisesforpatienceinanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 12:02:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000053_promisesforpatienceinanger/</guid>
      <description>But don’t let the passion of your emotions lead you to sin! Don’t let anger control you or be fuel for revenge, not for even a day. Don’t give the slanderous accuser, the Devil, an opportunity to manipulate you! Ephesians 4:26-27 TPT  Do you want to be a mighty warrior? It’s better to be known as one who is patient and slow to anger. Do you want to conquer a city?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The S.P.A.C.E. P.E.T.S. Method for Bible Study</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000050_thespacepetsmethod/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:29:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000050_thespacepetsmethod/</guid>
      <description>What is S.P.A.C.E. P.E.T.S.? Earlier this week, we talked about the S.O.A.P. Method for Bible study. Today, we&#39;ll talk about a method that can go hand-in-hand with it to help us with the &#34;Application&#34; part of the S.O.A.P. Method: S.P.A.C.E. P.E.T.S.
With space pets, you ask yourself if you can find any of these in the text:
  S: Sin to confess  P: Promise to claim  A: Attitude to change  C: Command to obey  E: Example to follow  P: Prayer to pray  E: Error to avoid  T: Truth to believe  S: Something to praise God for  When we try to apply the Bible to our lives, it can seem hard because the Bible is an ancient library of books written by and to an ancient people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The S.O.A.P. Method for Bible Study</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000049_thesoapmethod/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 17:45:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000049_thesoapmethod/</guid>
      <description>When we read the Bible, sometimes we just read the words on the page and move on. But what about when we want to get a little more understanding from the text? Is there a systematic way of breaking down scripture so that we get to its deeper meanings? There are actually many methods for this, but we&#39;ll focus on one today: The S.O.A.P. Method.
What Does SOAP Stand For?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bible Study Tools: Concordance</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000048_concordances/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 09:26:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000048_concordances/</guid>
      <description>What is a Bible concordance? A Bible concordance is an index of words used in the Bible and a reference for where each word occurs within the Bible.
There are many free online concordances, and you can also buy them in print.
 Why would I use a concordance? Concordances are useful for finding passages. Only remember one word from a passage you want to find? Looking for passages that refer to the same topics and concepts as the one you&#39;re reading?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running a Godly Business</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000044_runningagodlybusiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 11:58:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000044_runningagodlybusiness/</guid>
      <description>Running a business can be very stressful, but glory to God for taking the weight. He has given us wisdom for navigating deals and dilemnas! Let&#39;s look at some of the advice the Bible gives us about business.
Remember That it is Really God&#39;s Business It can be easy to think that the businesses we run are ours alone. But the truth is that we are stewarding all that we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution: The Biblical Way</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000043_conflictresoltion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:58:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000043_conflictresoltion/</guid>
      <description>Conflict is just a part of life. We will all at one point or another need tools to resolve it. Let&#39;s have a look at some Godly principles for handling times when we don&#39;t see eye to eye.
Avoid Strife and Argument Whenever Possible  The Bible tells us that we should try to avoid having the argument in the first place. This is not the same as &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Prayer in the Storm</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000040_yourprayerinthestorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 11:57:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000040_yourprayerinthestorm/</guid>
      <description>When we are in crisis circumstance can make us want to rush into action. We run forward to solve problems, forgetting that our first step should be prayer.
Here are a few short prayers that speak God&#39;s Word over our lives. Let&#39;s say what God says in this season.
Overcoming Worry Lord, I thank You for Your logic-defying peace as I come to Your throne.a Because I trust You, I know that You keep me in perfect peace and keep my mind whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Focus in the Storm</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000039_yourfocusinthestorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 11:57:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000039_yourfocusinthestorm/</guid>
      <description>When we are in crisis it can be hard to keep our focus in a healthy place. If we let our thoughts run wild, our fear can overwhelm us. But the Bible lets us know where our focus should lie.
Focus on Jesus We look away from the natural realm and we fasten our gaze onto Jesus who birthed faith within us and who leads us forward into faith’s perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Speech in the Storm</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000038_yourspeechinthestorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 11:56:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000038_yourspeechinthestorm/</guid>
      <description>When we are in crisis, our emotions can come to overtake us, and we speak rashly. But even as you walk through chaos, it&#39;s important to T.H.I.N.K. before you speak.
T: Is it True? Instead, speaking the truth in love, we will grow to become in every respect the mature body of him who is the head, that is, Christ. Ephesians 4:15 NIV
 H: Is it Helpful? Don’t use foul or abusive language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Only a Scarecrow</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000035_itsonlyascarecrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 13:06:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000035_itsonlyascarecrow/</guid>
      <description>Have you noticed that just as you&#39;re entering a growth season, you are often slammed with a trial?
Don&#39;t fear! It is only a scarecrow! Its purpose is to distract you from the bountiful fields just ahead!
And a man in the crowd shouted desperately, “Please, Teacher, I beg of you, do something about my boy. He’s my only child. He’s possessed by an evil spirit that makes him scream out in torment and hardly ever leaves him alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotting Condemnation Posing as Conviction: Finale</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000034_condemnationvsconviction_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000034_condemnationvsconviction_6/</guid>
      <description>This week, we examined the differences between conviction and condemnation. When trying to discern conviction from condemnation, try asking yourself these questions...
 Am I truly repenting of this sin? Or am I just trying to follow a rule? Is this thought designed to help me win? Or is telling me to give up? Is this making me want to try again after I&#39;ve fallen? Or is it making me want to wallow in guilt and regret?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotting Condemnation Posing as Conviction: Part 5</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000033_condemnationvsconviction_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000033_condemnationvsconviction_5/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, we saw how conviction gives us appetites for justice while condemnation ultimately pulls us to do wrong. Let&#39;s continue examining godly sorrow and how it contrasts with the sorrow of the world.
Conviction shows you how God sees you. We all sin and come short. God does not hide that fact, but when God views us, He does so in the light of Christ&#39;s sacrifice. So that though we are flawed, we are made righteous through the Son.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotting Condemnation Posing as Conviction: Part 4</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000032_condemnationvsconviction_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000032_condemnationvsconviction_4/</guid>
      <description>We saw how conviction brings us life and peace while condemnation brings us regret, anxiety, and death. Let&#39;s check out two more indicators of which influence we are dealing with.
Conviction makes you eager to do right Conviction gives you new appetites for good things. It shows you that your wrongdoings are not a part of your identity and exposes wonderful parts of you that were previously unseen.
Condemnation tells you that you can&#39;t do right Condemnation lies and says that sin is just who you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotting Condemnation Posing as Conviction: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000031_condemnationvsconviction_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000031_condemnationvsconviction_3/</guid>
      <description>Previously, we saw how condemnation leads us to legalism and failure while conviction leads us to repentance and victory. Let&#39;s continue to look at these two influences and their affect on the believer.
Conviction doesn&#39;t leave you in regret Conviction corrects without harping and badgering, peacefully pointing you in the right direction. You needn&#39;t feel lost in guilt. You are redeemed through Christ.
Condemnation covers you in the residue of your past Condemnation rehashes old wrongs and nags, even after you&#39;ve corrected course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotting Condemnation Posing as Conviction: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000030_condemnationvsconviction_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000030_condemnationvsconviction_2/</guid>
      <description>Last time, we looked at an illustration of godly sorrow and how it affects our lives. Let&#39;s start contrasting conviction from God with condemnation from the enemy.
True Conviction Leads to True Repentance Godly sorrow brings about a change of heart. It might make you a little sad, but that sadness quickly gives way to a renewed way of thinking.
Condemnation Just Leads to Legalism Condemnation causes forced behavioral change and rigid rule-following.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotting Condemnation Posing as Conviction: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000029_condemnationvsconviction_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000029_condemnationvsconviction_1/</guid>
      <description>One of the enemy&#39;s favorite tricks is to try to bring condemnation to God&#39;s people.
&#34;Satan&#34; means &#34;accuser&#34; and he never fails to live up to the title. But not only does he accuse, he lies and says it is coming from God!
Let&#39;s look at what Paul called &#34;godly sorrow,&#34; a perfect picture of Christian conviction.
Even if my letter made you sorrowful, I don’t regret sending it (even though I felt awful for a moment when I heard how it grieved you).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Forget to Mind Your Business!</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000028_mindthineown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000028_mindthineown/</guid>
      <description>The Bible is full of practical advice for life. Let’s look at what it says about meddling in other people’s affairs.
It’s better to grab a mad dog by its ears than to meddle and interfere in a quarrel that’s none of your business. Proverbs 26:17 TPT
 Aspire to lead a calm and peaceful life as you mind your own business and earn your living, just as we’ve taught you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Handle Exile</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000025_exilebehavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000025_exilebehavior/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dig Up Your Buried Dreams</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000024_godigitup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000024_godigitup/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living the &#39;Our Father&#39; Prayer Everyday</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000020_modelingthemodelprayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000020_modelingthemodelprayer/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Control of Your Thoughts!</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000017_takeeverythoughtcaptive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000017_takeeverythoughtcaptive/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change the Name, Change More?</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000016_whatsinaname/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000016_whatsinaname/</guid>
      <description>## Identities Under Attack Sometimes, our identities are called into question or even outright attacked. We&#39;ll look to the &#34;Three Hebrew Boys&#34; to find an example of what it looks like to withstand an attack on who we are.   The story of the Three Hebrew Boys may be familiar to you. These three young men were thrown into a large furnace as punishment for refusing to worship a statue of the king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the Sabbath?</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000014_rememberthesabbath/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000014_rememberthesabbath/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Are Not Too Young!</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000013_donotdespiseyouryouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000013_donotdespiseyouryouth/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Prayer for the Peace Maker</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000009_peacemakersprayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000009_peacemakersprayer/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Do I Put on the Garment of Praise?</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000008_garmentofpraise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000008_garmentofpraise/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Do I Start Reading the Bible?</title>
      <link>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000003_wheretostart/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://festive-mcclintock-6dbef7.netlify.app/posts/000003_wheretostart/</guid>
      <description>             View this post on Instagram                    A post shared by Tweets From Heaven (@tweets.from.heaven)
   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
